Sujal Anand

MuleSoft Developer

Contact



Lakhisarai, Bihar,811311



sujalanand056@gmail.com



08102716197



https://www.linkedin.com/in/suj al-anand-61324b142/

Skills

Java

MuleSoft

Web Service

JSON/XML

CI/CD

Jenkins

Salesforce Integration

Cloud Computing

GitHub

Docker

Kubernetes

DevOps

Public Cloud - AWS

Private Cloud - OpenShift

Hobbies

Bike riding, listening music, Foosball

I am a MuleSoft Developer with 2+ years of Experience in requirement analysis, designing, development, testing and implementation of business applications in MuleSoft and salesforce. Recognized consistently for performance excellence and contributions to success in IT industry. I am technology enthusiast, always keen to learn new technology.

Work History

MuleSoft Associate Consultant

June 2019 - April 2021, Wipro Ltd.

- I have Got ROAR Award, which is given to the person who has given Excellence performance in the project.
- I have Also given Training to My team member in MuleSoft DevOps.
 Developing Asset for the Internal team.

MuleSoft Developer

April 2021 - Present, Deloitte.

• I am a MuleSoft Developer

Education

2015- 2019	Bachelor of Technology
	Jaipur Engineering College - Jaipur
2013- 2014	Higher Secondary Vidya Bhawan Balika Vidyapeeth - Lakhisarai
2011- 2012	Secondary D.A.V Public School - Lakhisarai

Projects

- I have build a reusable generic batch job which will fetch data from Database and upsert it in Salesforce and make a response csv file later that file is send through email as an attachment.
- I have Used MuleSoft for Integration between SmapOne Cloud to SAP.
 Periodically fetching data from SmapOne and storing it in on the Azure Storage (Storing in Queue and then dequeuing was involved too).
- I have used MuleSoft to sync SQL Server with Salesforce. For triggering the APII have used Salesforce CDC.
- I have Created CI/CD Pipeline for Automated Deployment using Jenkins.

Certifications

- MCD Level 1 (Mule 4)
- MCD API Design Associate (RAML 1.0)
- Salesforce Certified Administrator
- Salesforce Certified Platform Developer I
- Red hat certified System Administrator
- Red hat certified Specialist in Ansible Automation
- Red hat certified Specialist in OpenShift Administration